|Anele Maseko | IT Graduate

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/anele-maseko-0763b2224

• Ivy Street, Ebony Park, Midrand 1632

0761378804

PROFILE

Recent graduate with a National Diploma in Information Technology (Software Development) and a passion for Information Technology it can be from Software Development, Cloud Computing etc. SDLC, with Experience in Manual Testing and a little bit of Automation Testing.

EDUCATION

Jerusalem sec School | White River

Jan 2009-2013

Subject Passed: English, SiSwati, Mathematics, Physical Science, Life Sciences, Geography Life Orientation

Tshwane University of Technology | Pretoria

Jan 2017-Sept 2022

National Diploma in IT Software Development

Key Modules: Communication Networks, Technical Programming, IT Mathematics, Data analysis, Structured Query languages

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Class monitor in High School (2013)
- Did an e-commerce project for the school (2021)
- Did an online application website for a school at Adom Technologies (2022)

SKILLS

Languages: English (Fluent), SiSwati (Fluent), Sepedi (Fluent), Zulu (Fluent)

Strong work ethic and ability to function well in a team

Excellent time management, Problem Solver

Good interpersonal skills, Analytical thinking

Work well under pressure and meet deadlines

Self-Motivation, drive and energy

Continuous passion for learning Team

working skills, Multitasking

SOL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, C++, PHP, C#, React, node.is, Jira, Git and Github,

PhpMyAdmin (Basics), Linux (Basics), Remote Support (AnyDesk),

Agile.

Experience

Adom Technologies | Nelspruit

Aug 2022-Jul 2023

WIL Program: Software Development

Key Responsibility

- Developing Softwares
- Upgrading of software
- Database management

CapaCiti / UVUAfrica | Johannesburg

Aug 2023- present

Internship: Software Development/Tester/DevOps

Key Responsibility

- Software Development
- Continuous Integration and continuous delivery
- Familiar with Selenium and Jenkins.
- Writing script in Selenium for testing the application e.g Testing new features.
- Developed and Executed test cases
- Manual Testing
- Works closely with development team to identify and report defects.

Skills: Automation Testing, Manual Testing, JIRA, Jenkins, JavaScript, HTML, Python, SQL, Linux

<u>References</u>

Adom Techologies: mentor | Chris Sifundza

Position: Senior Software developer

Contacts: 073 614 4461

GNS: mentor | Mr Brian Mkasi

Position: Support Manager/ Project Manager

Contacts: 079